{
    "results": [
    

        {
    
    "question": "Internal energy of a system is",
    "correct_answer": "all the above",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "vibrational energy",
        "linear kinetic energy",
        "rotational and potential energy"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Indicators are used to detect the nature of the solution for",
    "correct_answer": "D.Both A and B",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "A.Acidity",
        "B.Basicity",
        "C.None of these"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "……………….. taste is a characteristic property of all acids in aqueous solutions",
    "correct_answer": "Sour",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Bitter",
        "Salty",
        "Sweet"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Bases tend to taste …………….. and feel …………",
    "correct_answer": "Bitter, slippery to touch",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Sour, pleasant to touch",
        "Sour, slippery to touch",
        "None of these"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Acids turn …………… litmus to ………………..litmus",
    "correct_answer": "Blue, red",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Red, red",
        "Blue, red",
        "Red, blue"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Natural indicators are prepared from…..",
    "correct_answer": "Both i and iii",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Plants",
        "Petrochemicals",
        "Minerals"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Natural indicators among these",
    "correct_answer": "i, ii and iv",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Litmus",
        "Methyl orange",
        "Turmeric"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "The colour of turmeric in basic solutions is………",
    "correct_answer": "Red",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Blue",
        "Green",
        "Orange"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Synthetic indicator among these",
    "correct_answer": "All of these",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Methyl red",
        "Phenolphthalein",
        "Methyl orange"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "The colour of turmeric in basic solutions is………",
    "correct_answer": "Red",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Blue",
        "Green",
        "Orange"
    ]
},
{
    "question": "Synthetic indicator among these",
    "correct_answer": "All of these",
    "incorrect_answers": [
        "Methyl red",
        "Phenolphthalein",
        "Methyl orange"
    ]
}
    ]
}
